Contact

lucasneri.mat@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/lucasneri99 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Mathematics

Physical Sciences

Front-End Development

Certifications

Introdução a criação de websites com HTML5 e CSS3

Desenvolvimento avançado com JavaScript ES6

Trabalhando com Componentes em React

Conceitos de responsividade e experiência do usuário

Introdução ao ReactJS

Lucas Neri

Frontend Developer

Belo Horizonte

Summary

I'm a multidisciplinary software engineer with more than two years of experience. As designing, developing, and supporting robust applications, these are used by thousands of people, every day.

I normally work with Javascript, Typescript, Vue, React, Golang, Mysql, MongoDB and Docker, but I have also experience with Python. My interest areas are Distributed Systems, Networks, and Operating Systems.

I'm currently trying to improve, increasing knowledge about softwaredefined networks and fast packet processing technologies

You can see some of my work at lucasneri.com

Experience

EstrelaBet

Frontend Developer

June 2022 - Present (2 months)

Belo Horizonte, Minas Gerais, Brasil

Working on the internal system team, supporting integrations used by Vue, React, Typescript, Javascript, Golang, Mongo, Mysql, Docker and other, helping them to drive better outcomes in all services.

Grupo SX

Software Developer

June 2021 - July 2022 (1 year 2 months)

Belo Horizonte, Minas Gerais, Brasil

My main activity is to bring improvements to the system, adding and updating tools.

I work with Golang, Javascript, Typescript, Python, MongoDB, MYSQL, Docker, Swagger, Jira, Vue, Node, React, and others.

upFlow.me Software Analyst September 2021 - October 2021 (2 months) Belo Horizonte, Minas Gerais, Brasil

Self-employed
Mathematics Teacher
July 2019 - February 2021 (1 year 8 months)
Minas Gerais, Brasil

Private teacher for high school students.

Localiza Hertz
Call Center Agent
October 2018 - February 2019 (5 months)
Cachoeirinha, Minas Gerais

Sagendra Trainee August 2015 - July 2016 (1 year) Camargos, Minas Gerais

Education

Universidade Federal de Minas Gerais

Bachelor of Mathematic, Mathematics and Computer Science · (2019 - 2024)

Uptime

English Course, English Language and Literature/Letters · (2016 - 2017)

Colégio Tiradentes da PMMG High School Diploma · (2015 - 2017)